Diseases and illnesses are like uninvited guests. They
never come with any warning,
but whenever they do arrive, it's our job to be
financially prepared for them. Financial
preparation means being prepared. Hi, my name is
Muskan, and today I'm here to tell you about Digit Diamond
Line. Digit Diamond Line provides
Simple Five general insurance
solutions to all its customers. Its mission is to make the
entire health insurance process
simple and easy for its customers.
This insurance plan
covers every small and big expense of the sick person, so you
can get treatment without spending a fortune.
According to our expert research, this
insurance plan is one of the top 5 insurance plans.
So let's explore the
features of the Money Plan. Diamond Line has
features like no room rent, no
claim bonus option, maternity benefit, and
post-
hospitalization
photocopy. This means that if your
hospital bed is charged Rs. 10,000, your
insurance company will collect a fixed
amount for it, for example, Rs.
8,000.  The
speciality of this plan is that the
insurance company will bear the entire cost and the customer will
not have to pay anything from his pocket. The
entire cost as per the plan will be borne by the insurance company without any percentage
charge. There is
a limit on room rent in the insurance policy, such as one per cent
of the total body language. This means
that you can book any room of your choice during your period
without any worry
because there is no upper limit on room rent in this plan.
If you go through a whole year without any claim, then a
no claim bonus amount will be
added to your insurance as a bonus. If you want, you
can avail the maternity benefit which covers
all the medical expenses of pregnancy.
This plan covers every expense from
tests and checkups before hospitalization to
medicines and flops after discharge. So,
this plan
develops amazing benefits of Diamond to know more about it visit www.com